{
    "subject": "resource/Spider-Man_Unlimited",
    "predicate": "property/writer",
    "object": "resource/Robert_Gregory_Browne",
    "human_readable": "The writer of Spider-Man Unlimited is Robert Gregory Browne.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.988642156124115,
            "question": "Is Robert Gregory Browne the writer of Spider-Man Unlimited?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9403747320175171,
            "question": "Name the author of Spider-Man Unlimited."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8958097696304321,
            "question": "Who wrote Spider-Man Unlimited?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8730756640434265,
            "question": "Which writer penned the story of Spider-Man Unlimited?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8584945797920227,
            "question": "What is the name of the writer for Spider-Man Unlimited?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7793754935264587,
            "question": "Can you tell me the author of Spider-Man Unlimited?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.634588897228241,
            "question": "Who created the story for Spider-Man Unlimited?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6187319159507751,
            "question": "What comic book series did Robert Gregory Browne write?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5391836166381836,
            "question": "Robert Gregory Browne is associated with which comic book?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47826093435287476,
            "question": "What comic book series is Robert Gregory Browne known for?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The writer of Spider-Man Unlimited is Robert Gregory Browne.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3284_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Robert Gregory Browne is associated with which comic book?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3284_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What comic book series did Robert Gregory Browne write?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3284_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who created the story for Spider-Man Unlimited?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3284_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3284_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3284_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3284_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3284_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3284_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3284_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3284_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3284_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3284_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3284_6.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that \"Larry Brody, Robert Gregory Browne, Brynne Chandler, and Michael Reaves\" were the writers for the TV series Spider-Man Unlimited. Therefore, the statement that \"The writer of Spider-Man Unlimited is Robert Gregory Browne\" is supported by the provided information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}